usage: Dependency-Check Core [--advancedHelp] [--disableVersionCheck]
       [--enableExperimental] [--exclude <pattern>] [-f <format>]
       [--failOnCVSS <score>] [-h] [--junitFailOnCVSS <score>] [-l <file>]
       [-n] [--nvdApiKey <apiKey>] [-o <path>] [--prettyPrint] [--project
       <name>] [-s <path>] [--suppression <file>] [-v]

Dependency-Check Core can be used to identify if there are any known CVE
vulnerabilities in libraries utilized by an application. Dependency-Check
Core will automatically update required data from the Internet, such as
the CVE and CPE data files from nvd.nist.gov.

    --advancedHelp              Print the advanced help message.
    --disableVersionCheck       Disables the dependency-check version
                                check
    --enableExperimental        Enables the experimental analyzers.
    --exclude <pattern>         Specify an exclusion pattern. This option
                                can be specified multiple times and it
                                accepts Ant style exclusions.
 -f,--format <format>           The report format (HTML, XML, CSV, JSON,
                                JUNIT, SARIF, JENKINS, GITLAB or ALL). The
                                default is HTML. Multiple format
                                parameters can be specified.
    --failOnCVSS <score>        Specifies if the build should be failed if
                                a CVSS score above a specified level is
                                identified. The default is 11; since the
                                CVSS scores are 0-10, by default the build
                                will never fail.
 -h,--help                      Print this message.
    --junitFailOnCVSS <score>   Specifies the CVSS score that is
                                considered a failure when generating the
                                junit report. The default is 0.
 -l,--log <file>                The file path to write verbose logging
                                information.
 -n,--noupdate                  Disables the automatic updating of the
                                NVD-CVE, hosted-suppressions and RetireJS
                                data.
    --nvdApiKey <apiKey>        The API Key to access the NVD API.
 -o,--out <path>                The folder to write reports to. This
                                defaults to the current directory. It is
                                possible to set this to a specific file
                                name if the format argument is not set to
                                ALL.
    --prettyPrint               When specified the JSON and XML report
                                formats will be pretty printed.
    --project <name>            The name of the project being scanned.
 -s,--scan <path>               The path to scan - this option can be
                                specified multiple times. Ant style paths
                                are supported (e.g. 'path/**/*.jar'); if
                                using Ant style paths it is highly
                                recommended to quote the argument value.
    --suppression <file>        The file path to the suppression XML file.
                                This can be specified more then once to
                                utilize multiple suppression files
 -v,--version                   Print the version information.
